Jiang Zhaoguo.
Jiang Zhaoguo.
Don't hit it again!
别再打了！
Quickly grab a knife
赶紧拿起刀
knife!
刀！
Take the knife.
拿刀。
Quickly grab a knife.
赶紧拿起刀。
Why are you silent?
你为什么沉默？
Knife!
刀！
The knife comes.
刀来了。
Kill him
杀了他
fast!
快速地！
Attack.
攻击。
Kill him!
杀了他！
Quickly kill him!
快杀了他！
Fast!
快速地！
Why are you still silent?
为什么你还是沉默？
Quickly kill him!
快杀了他！
Fast!
快速地！
Quick, help me take care of this corpse.
快帮我处理一下这具尸体。
Why are you still silent?
为什么你还是沉默？
Hurry up.
赶快。
Come in
进来
why did you come home so late?
你怎么这么晚才回家？
Didn't you hear?
你没听到吗？
Recently our business has experienced big problems.
最近我们的业务遇到了很大的问题。
Commander Luo arrested CCP members,
罗司令抓捕中共党员，
and also the head of the transportation station.
也是交通站站长。
The level is not low
水平不低
but I didn't think so
但我不这么认为
the CCP's underground party
中共地下党
is the owner of the book and painting shop Yumo, owner Lu
是书画店雨墨的老板，陆老板
Lu's boss is the Underground Party of the Chinese Communist Party
卢老板是中共地下党
really didn't expect it
真的没想到
CCP underground party
中共地下党
CCP special agents are everywhere.
中共特务无处不在。
Because he is a leader,
因为他是领导者，
there must be a lot of information.
一定有很多信息。
In that case,
在这种情况下，
will make a major contribution?
会做出重大贡献吗？
What report?
什么报告？
What services do you provide?
你提供什么服务？
Boss Lu is in order to protect his colleagues,
陆老板为了保护同事，
didn't say a word.
没有说一句话。
Better to die than give up.
与其放弃，不如死掉。
I have heard
我听说
CCP people are all brave
共产党人都是勇敢的
you've seen it, right?
你已经看过了，对吧？
These are all Boss Lu's data,
这些都是陆老板的数据，
and interrogation recordings.
以及审讯录音。
I have to tidy everything up.
我必须把一切都收拾干净。
Tomorrow we still have to hand it over to Commander Luo.
明天还要交给罗司令。
How to make?
怎么做？
I'll sleep for a while.
我再睡一会儿吧。
Talk about it later.
稍后再说。
You sleep quickly
你睡得很快
why did you change your phone number
你为什么改变你的电话号码
I can't find you.
我找不到你。
I don't want to see you again
我不想再见到你
Why?
为什么？
You asked me why
你问我为什么
don't you know what you have done
你不知道你做了什么吗
How long will you lie to me?
你还要骗我多久？
You...
你...
I already know.
我已经知道了。
I don't have any feelings for that woman.
我对那个女人没有任何感情。
She is Director Liu's daughter.
她是刘主任的女儿。
I just need him...
我只需要他...
Helped me get some things done.
帮助我完成了一些事情。
It turns out you can speak so confidently.
原来你能这么自信地说话。
Now I'm in this position.
现在我就处于这个位置。
I have to take advantage
我必须利用
all the power around me that can be used.
我周围所有可以使用的力量。
I can not do anything.
我什么都做不了。
You don't understand politics,
你不懂政治
you're too innocent
你太无辜了
However,...
然而，...
This is also the reason I love you.
这也是我爱你的原因。
Love me?
爱我？
You still say things like this now.
你现在还说这样的话。
Isn't that very ironic?
这不是很讽刺吗？
Can we not discuss this matter first?
我们能不能先讨论一下这个问题？
Ding Qiuyang was a member of the mountain's subordinate army.
丁秋阳是山下军中的一员。
This time I came to Shanghai for a secret mission.
这次我来上海是执行秘密任务的。
If he knew,...
如果他知道的话……
The fighters will know I'm coming to Shanghai.
战士们会知道我要来上海。
Do you know?
你知道吗？
Looks like it's pretty close here.
看来这里已经很近了。
Wait
等待
how did you know Ding Qiuyang
你怎么认识丁秋阳的
help the mountain's subordinates.
帮助山下的属下。
Back when you introduced me to him
当你把我介绍给他的时候
just said he was a famous director.
刚才说他是一个著名的导演。
Let's treat the corpse first.
我们先处理一下尸体吧。
Perhaps not?
也许不是？
No.
不。
I told you to tell me now
我告诉过你现在就告诉我
Good.
好的。
Then I'll tell you
那我就告诉你
that day at the Hollywood bar,
那天在好莱坞酒吧，
I've met him.
我见过他。
Why did you meet him?
你为什么遇见他？
I was forced.
我是被迫的。
At that time, I had an important document in my hand.
当时我手里拿着一份重要的文件。
He said if I take you away,
他说如果我带你走
then will send me to the military headquarters.
然后就会送我去军事总部。
So,
所以，
actually you were the one who sold me.
其实你才是卖掉我的人。
That's right, right?
没错，对吧？
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
How can I sell you?
我怎样才能卖给你？
I think first
我认为首先
you really have to
你真的必须
that's why you can't take me away.
这就是为什么你不能带我走。
I didn't think you were the ones who had negotiated it
我没想到你们是协商的人
what tactics
什么战术
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
I know.
我知道。
I know you can't possibly give up your career
我知道你不可能放弃你的事业
shan Xia said he can help you in your career
山霞说他可以在你的事业上帮助你
so I thought
所以我认为
wouldn't it be great if you
如果你这样不是很好吗
isn't that a good thing?
这不是一件好事吗？
You're shameless!
你真是无耻啊！
Han Lu.
Han Lu.
Cold dew.
寒露。
What do you want?
你想要什么？
let me go
让我走
Why
为什么
Why?
为什么？
Why did you have to hurt me like this?
你为什么要这样伤害我？
You calm down a bit, okay?
你冷静一点，好吗？
Let's finish the body first.
我们先完成身体。
I just told you.
我刚刚告诉过你了。
Perhaps not?
也许不是？
Do you know?
你知道吗？
If the Japanese know I'm coming to Shanghai,
如果日本人知道我要来上海的话
then I will die.
那么我就会死。
Understand?
理解？
You make me very sad
你让我很伤心
lu Yousheng.
lu Yousheng.
Correct
正确的
all the way is clear
一路畅通
1927 AD
公元1927年
join the Chinese Communist Party
加入中国共产党
why should you join the Communist Party?
你为什么要加入共产党？
For faith's sake.
为了信仰。
Do you understand what faith is?
你明白什么是信仰吗？
Of course I don't understand.
我当然不明白。
their names,
他们的名字，
do you think I can say it?
你认为我可以说吗？
Of course I have a family.
当然，我有一个家庭。
Who doesn't have a family?
谁没有家庭？
It's just that I couldn't protect them well.
只是我没能很好的保护他们。
Well.
出色地。
I have many tasks.
我有很多任务。
Due to beliefs and doctrines
由于信仰和教义
you do not understand.
你不明白。
Then I'll say something you'll understand.
那我就说一句你能明白的话。
My mission is
我的使命是
is to make every Chinese person
就是要让每一个中国人
when they got home
当他们回到家时
what they see is not fear,
他们看到的不是恐惧，
not fear,
不害怕，
nor the cold corpses of his wife and child.
也没有他妻子和孩子冰冷的尸体。
All he saw were the smiling faces of his family.
他看到的只是家人的笑脸。
Happiness.
幸福。
But hope.
但希望。
This...
这...
It's my job.
这是我的工作。
It is our duty to every communist
这是我们对每一个共产党人的责任
do you understand?
你明白吗？
Have you written it down?
你写下来了吗？
Good
好的
I can't wait until that day comes
我等不及那一天的到来
but there are people who will come.
但还是有人会来。
40 thousand Chinese compatriots will wait until
4万中国同胞将等到
that day
那天
referred to as the new China
简称新中国
did someone steal the body?
有人偷走了尸体吗？
Ding Qiuyang is not dead at all?
丁秋阳根本就没有死？
I was too careless.
我太粗心了。
Why kill Ding Qiuyang?
Why kill Ding Qiuyang?
This time I came to Shanghai
这次我来上海
do you want to negotiate?
你想谈判吗？
with a code name?
有代号吗？
He holds something I want.
他手里拿着我想要的东西。
But this thing
但这件事
the Japanese also wanted to get it.
日本人也想得到它。
Japanese people in Chongqing,
在重庆的日本人，
put a lot of spies,
派出大量间谍，
so they already know
所以他们已经知道了
chongqing sent people to Shanghai
重庆派人前往上海
but they don't know
但他们不知道
the one they sent was me
他们派来的就是我
jika Ding Qiuyang ini
jika Ding Qiuyang ini
told my identity to the Japanese
把我的身份告诉日本人
even said
甚至说
the Japanese discovered the magpie before me,
日本人在我之前发现了喜鹊，
then my mission this time really failed.
那么我这次的任务就真的失败了。
Then I can go find a mountain subordinate to test it.
那我就可以去找山部属去测试一下了。
Looking for what?
寻找什么？
Did Ding Qiuyang find the foot of the mountain?
丁秋阳找到山脚了吗？
Does the foot of the mountain know all this?
山脚下知道这一切吗？
You can't go
你不能走
This is too dangerous.
这太危险了。
Won't.
惯于。
Why?
为什么？
Because he loves me.
因为他爱我。
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
He loves me.
他爱我。
maybe,
或许，
love me more than you
爱我胜过爱你
qian Xiu Cai
qian Xiu Cai
koran
古兰经
here.
这里。
New declaration.
新宣言。
News report.
新闻报道。
Good.
好的。
Not true.
不对。
Why less than one page?
为什么少于一页？
Why is there one page less?
为什么少了一页？
What's missing is the series page.
缺少的是系列页面。
Fast.
快速地。
Help me search.
帮我搜一下。
Then I'll look for it.
那我就去找找吧。
This story is in a time of crisis,
这个故事发生在一个危机时刻，
zhen Fei ingin membunuh Jiang Xiao He.
zhen Fei ingin membunuh Jiang Xiao He.
Jiang Xiao He didn't know that he intended to kill.
江小荷并不知道他是想杀人。
No.
不。
If not,
如果不，
where are Captain Zhao and Manager Luo's newspapers?
赵队长和罗经理的报纸在哪里？
I've delivered it to the front door.
我已经把它送到前门了。
You can borrow them for a while.
你可以借用一段时间。
Makes sense.
说得通。
Finally back
终于回来了
leader
领导者
the office has been cleaned.
办公室已经打扫干净了。
As the saying goes, back to a new atmosphere
俗话说，回到新气象
open the door to meet the far away
打开门迎接远方
Chen's head
陈的头像
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Ketua Zhao.
Ketua Zhao.
Already home
已经到家了
surprise no?
惊讶不？
Safe, safe.
安全，安全。
I'm looking for newspapers here.
我正在这里找报纸。
What newspapers are you looking for at my place?
你在我家找什么报纸？
The martial arts novel featured in this new statement,
此次新声明中的武侠小说，
kun Lun who was surprised.
昆仑惊讶道。
I don't know why I didn't order anything
我不知道为什么我没有订购任何东西
Qian Xiu said that the newspapers had been placed here
千修说报纸就放在这里了
so I came to look for him
所以我来找他
have found?
已经发现？
Have found.
已经发现。
Here.
这里。
Look at it.
看它。
Kun Lun?
Kun Lun?
Captain Zhao is back.
赵队长回来了。
Your newspaper, I remain motionless.
你的报纸，我一动不动。
I put it here.
我把它放在这里。
You tell me after reading it.
你看完后告诉我。
I came to get it.
我是来拿的。
I go first.
我先走了。
Go ahead.
前进。
Safe, safe.
安全，安全。
What do you want, boss?
老板你想要什么？
Undress.
脱衣服。
Komandan Luo.
Komandan Luo.
Can you still sit?
还能坐吗？
What is it?
它是什么？
Zhao An.
Zhao An.
You did not know?
你不知道？
Of course I know
我当然知道
he was clearly an important person in the CCP that we arrested.
他显然是我们抓捕的中共重要人物。
We didn't get any prizes.
我们没有得到任何奖品。
Zhao An is back to work?
赵安回来上班了？
On what basis?
依据什么？
As expected.
正如预期的那样。
Do you think Kimura will let him keep a horse?
你觉得木村会让他养马吗？
What you mean is...
你的意思是...
Already thought of a way to deal with Zhao An, right?
已经想好办法对付赵安了吧？
We will monitor the changes.
我们将监控变化。
Don't want chaos.
不想混乱。
Old Fox.
老狐狸。
What are you looking for?
你要买什么？
I've found it, I've found it.
我找到了，我找到了。
There's another series to check out.
还有另一个系列值得一看。
What's that?
那是什么？
This Zhen Fei, still can't intervene.
这个甄妃，还插手不了。
The tension will soon be revealed.
紧张的气氛很快就会显露出来。
I still feel like the feeling here is not right.
我还是觉得这里的感觉不太对劲。
Yesterday, when I opened the window all day, the wind was strong.
昨天，我整天打开窗户，风很大。
The smell is not right.
气味不对。
Basically not true.
基本上不是真的。
Salah.
萨拉赫。
This scent is simply not right
这气味根本就不对劲
there is no longer the smell of horse manure
不再有马粪的味道
not accustomed to.
不习惯。
Sis,
姐姐，
if we go
如果我们去
What about Xiao Douzi in the future?
小豆子以后怎么办？
Don't think about Xiao Douzi anymore.
别再想小豆子了。
Village Chief Mu wants to expel him,
穆村长要开除他，
from now on he is a Japanese horse.
从此他就是一匹日本马了。
It will be better than our fate.
这会比我们的命运更好。
How did it happen?
它是怎么发生的？
Who in Japan knows Xiao Douzi's habits?
日本谁知道小豆子的习惯呢？
This seed likes to eat alfalfa.
这种种子喜欢吃苜蓿。
He doesn't like peanuts.
他不喜欢花生。
He likes rubber horse brushes.
他喜欢橡胶马刷。
Doesn't like iron combs.
不喜欢铁梳。
Go with them.
和他们一起去吧。
Don't be picky here
这里不要挑剔
Just keeping a horse is no longer exciting.
仅仅养一匹马已经不再令人兴奋了。
What do you think I can do with you?
你觉得我能对你做什么？
Tree trunk.
树干。
Yesterday A-Chuan and Xiao Lai Zi.
Yesterday A-Chuan and Xiao Lai Zi.
Pretty good.
不错。
Officially recruit them
正式招募他们
I want to reorganize my troops
我要重组我的部队
Good.
好的。
10 shots.
10 次射击。
Since childhood,
从小时候起，
never been humiliated like this.
从来没有受过这样的羞辱。
Or I hit myself.
或者我自己打自己。
= Juara dunia = Luo Guanqun.
= Juara dunia = Luo Guanqun.
You have to remember.
你必须记住。
Want to embarrass Luo Guan Qun,
想要给罗冠群难堪，
should start from Chen Jia Ping
应该从陈家平开始
the one who went to the tea shop and took the old road was him
去茶馆走老路的就是他
He was the one who came to the bookstore and made a mess.
就是他来了书店，把书店弄得一团糟。
And also the action of arresting the negotiator yesterday.
还有昨天逮捕谈判代表的行动。
Every time something bad happens,
每当有不好的事情发生时，
there must be him
一定有他
Oh yes
哦是的
Lao Tian's people wanted notice at that time,
老田的人当时要通知，
which newspaper is it in?
刊登在哪份报纸上？
New statement?
新声明？
Correct.
正确的。
This new statement includes a series of martial arts novels.
这个新的说法包括一系列武侠小说。
Kun Lun was surprised.
昆仑吃了一惊。
I don't know why I didn't order anything
我不知道为什么我没有订购任何东西
Qian Xiu said that the newspapers had been placed here
千修说报纸就放在这里了
so I came looking for him.
所以我来找他。
Well then, missing person search notice,
那么，失踪人员搜寻通知，
It was a secret code for communication with the CCP
这是与中共通讯的暗号
so why Chen Jiaping
so why Chen Jiaping
Want to make this new declaration soon?
想尽快做出新的声明吗？
A-chuan as a fellow Xiao Lai Zi.
阿川饰演同乡小来子。
As they squatted in Yu Mo's calligraphy and painting shop,
当他们蹲在于墨的字画店里时，
Chen Jia Ping also came
陈家平也来了
at that time he moved several villas and treasures.
当时他搬走了几栋别墅和珍宝。
Do you think he meant something else?
你认为他还有别的意思吗？
Panggil Qian Xiu Cai kesini
Panggil Qian Xiu Cai kesini
Good
好的
kapten Zhao,
kapten Zhao,
if you say it is also very strange
如果你说这也很奇怪
Chen's section chief
陈科长
I used to hate seeing new announcements.
我曾经讨厌看到新的公告。
It's all just a cliché,
这一切都只是陈词滥调？？
but don't know why lately
但最近不知道为什么
very attentive to new reports.
非常关注新的报道。
Every day he immediately asked if the news had arrived or not
每天他都会立即询问消息是否到达
I know.
我知道。
Get out.
出去。
Wait.
等待。
This is what I'm asking you
这就是我要问你的
the thing I asked you.
我问你的事。
Understand?
理解？
Understand.
理解。
Ketua Zhao,
Ketua Zhao,
according to you, my observational abilities
根据你的说法，我的观察能力
not bad right?
不错吧？
Too good.
太好了。
Ketua Zhao
Ketua Zhao
even though I'm just a doorman,
虽然我只是个看门人
but I can still do it
但我仍然可以做到
other things and so on
其他事情等等
what else do you want to do?
你还想做什么？
You just be the manager.
你只是当经理。
It's been a joke.
这是一个笑话。
Kapten Zhao.
Kapten Zhao.
If there's anything, just call me.
有什么事就给我打电话。
I go first
我先走
Chen Jia Ping, these two days
陈家平 这两天
why rush to see the new declaration
为何急于看到新的宣言
because Lu is his boss.
因为陆是他的老板。
After Lao Lu died,
老鲁去世后，
there will be a new boss who wants to work with him.
将会有一个新老板想和他一起工作。
And the secret code for this connection
以及此连接的密码
it's in the new announcement.
这是新公告中的内容。
But all this,
但这一切，
obituary announcements and others,
讣告及其他，
more clearly which is the secret connecting code,
更清楚哪个是秘密连接代码，
we don't understand either.
我们也不明白。
We don't understand.
我们不明白。
Someone understands
有人明白
is indeed a genuine Bordeaux grape
确实是真正的波尔多葡萄
Haven't tasted this taste in a long time.
好久没有尝到这个味道了。
Ketua Zhao.
Ketua Zhao.
Eat it.
吃了它。
So I don't drink anymore.
所以我不再喝酒了。
If Brother Huang likes it,
如果黄哥喜欢的话
I'll get someone to deliver a few more bottles.
我会让人再送几瓶。
Agreed.
同意。
I've stayed a few days here.
我在这里呆了几天。
At that time we had an agreement.
那时我们有一个协议。
Chief Kimura of the Military Police Headquarters wants to see me.
宪兵司令部的木村局长要见我。
Until now it is still not visible.
直到现在还看不到。
I've told Village Chief Mu,
我跟穆村长说过，
It is just...
这只是...
Just what?
只是什么？
Brother Huang, I am not covering anything up.
黄兄，我没有隐瞒什么。
Your gift is not heavy enough.
你的礼物还不够重。
I've given everyone a list of the names of transportation station number five
我给大家列出了五号交通站的名字
giving is still not heavy enough.
付出还是不够重。
Despite arresting several people
尽管逮捕了数人
but just an ordinary person.
但只是一个普通人。
The Military Police Soldier Commander's appetite was growing.
宪兵司令的胃口越来越大。
Yumo bookstore security code,
语墨书店防伪码，
I've given it to you.
我已经给你了。
Not arresting people
不抓人
You can't blame me right?
你不能怪我吧？
The name of this Plum Blossom Si,
这个梅花寺的名字，
sister Huang ever heard of it?
黄姐听说过吗？
Plum blossom four.
梅花四朵。
Our people?
我们的人？
Chinese Communist Party codenamed Meihua Si.
中国共产党代号梅花寺。
Has been hiding in Taihe Company for a long time.
已经在太和公司躲藏了很长时间了。
Now I
现在我
I have a clear target of suspicion.
我有明确的怀疑目标。
As long as you help me find evidence,
只要你帮我找到证据
I promise,
我保证，
not only arranged for you to meet Village Chief Mu,
不仅安排你见到穆村长，
I will fulfill
我会履行
I will fulfill them one by one, will not deny them.
我会一一履行，不会否认。
But I don't know him.
但我不认识他。
How can I help you?
我怎么帮你？
Help me read the newspaper
帮我看报纸
what does it mean?
这是什么意思？
Bulletin board.
布告栏。
Those of you who want to find someone else.
你们中那些想找别人的人。
Why?
为什么？
The word "seeking brother" to pay the new year,
“求兄弟”二字交新年，
is our secret code.
是我们的密码。
Continue.
继续。
Brother has been in Shanghai for several days,
兄弟来上海好几天了，
This means wanting to connect.
这意味着想要连接。
I can't find you at your original address, 220.
我在你原来的地址 220 找不到你。
This is the time.
现在是时候了。
This afternoon at 2:20
今天下午 2:20
The second sister at Zhou Jian's house
周建家二姐
3rd younger brother, Shan Ming was very worried about him.
三弟山明很担心他。
Boat?
船？
Mountain.
山。
Is there a place in Shanghai that says "Zhou and Shan"?
上海有没有地方说“周山”？
Taman Zhoushan.
舟山花园.
The connection location is Zhoushan Park.
接驳地点为舟山公园。
Correct.
正确的。
Now I am staying temporarily on the fifth floor of Pujiang Inn.
现在我暂时住在浦江宾馆五楼。
Pujiang is a place associated with water.
浦江是一个与水有关的地方。
Is there a pond in Zhoushan Park?
舟山公园有池塘吗？
I once went to Zhoushan Park.
我曾经去过舟山公园。
Pond?
池塘？
There isn't any.
没有。
If there's water,
如果有水的话
there is a fountain.
有一个喷泉。
It's a fountain
这是一个喷泉
the fifth floor is the fifth bench.
五楼是第五条长凳。
That means 14.20 this afternoon,
也就是说今天下午14.20，
di Taman Zhoushan,
di Taman Zhoushan,
beside the fountain,
在喷泉旁边，
must be CCP.
一定是中共。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
Cheers.
干杯。
Until found.
直到被发现。
This.
这。
Thank You.
谢谢。
One more time.
再一次。
Good.
好的。
Why stop the mission?
为什么要停止任务？
You've missed the best opportunity.
你已经错过了最好的机会。
But I already have a clue
但我已经有了线索
give me one more day.
再给我一天时间。
This is an order.
这是命令。
Good.
好的。
Then you can tell me
那你可以告诉我
what is in the magpie's hand?
喜鹊手里拿着什么？
It doesn't matter if I tell you.
我告诉你也没关系。
A formula
一个公式
formula?
公式？
Correct
正确的
the Chinese Communist Party plans
中国共产党的计划
will gradually issue sideways coins
将逐步发行横版币
at banks in the border areas of Shaanxi and Ganning,
陕西、甘宁边境地区的银行，
to replace French money
取代法国货币
and build their own financial system.
并建立自己的金融体系。
Apart from that, they are also developing
除此之外，他们还正在开发
special paper for printing money
印钞专用纸
making their currency difficult to counterfeit.
使他们的货币难以伪造。
Therefore, within the squad,
因此，在球队内部，
sent two special agents to scout in Yan'an,
派出两名特工到延安侦察，
to investigate border money printing
调查边境印钞
and also information about the publisher.
以及有关出版商的信息。
The magpie is one of them.
喜鹊就是其中之一。
But unexpectedly this person
却没想到这个人
after getting mysterious information
得到神秘信息后
he immediately used this as a threat
他立即以此作为威胁
for us to pay sky-high prices?
让我们付出天价？
How can there be such scum in the government?
政府里怎么会有这样的败类？
Chongqing can't wait
重庆已经等不及了
they had to get the formula as soon as possible
他们必须尽快得到配方
So, Boss Dai...
那么戴老板...
Already agreed to a sky-high price.
已经答应了天价。
The person he sent has arrived in Shanghai.
他派的人已经到了上海。
They will immediately make a transaction.
他们将立即进行交易。
I don't understand
我不明白
why do we want a money printing paper formula
为什么我们需要印钞纸配方
if we fake it
如果我们假装它
can counterfeit real money
可以伪造真钱
and put it in the border area
并把它放在边界区域
new financial system
新金融体系
financial system
金融系统
will collapse in an instant.
会瞬间崩溃。
We don't have to fire a single shot
我们不必开一枪
to destroy the nest of the Communist Party.
摧毁共产党的老巢。
But doing it like this,
但这样做的话，
isn't it a violation at all?
这根本不违规吗？
statement of cooperation between the state and the Communist Party.
国家与共产党合作声明。
You're too innocent.
你太无辜了。
When have the Kuomintang and the Communist Party ever had real cooperation?
国共两党什么时候真正合作过？
Previously restricted collusion,
此前限制共谋，
now it has become a real anti-communist.
现在已经成为真正的反共分子了。
In the Communist Party,
在共产党内，
there are many brave warriors
有许多勇敢的战士
they are willing to sacrifice their lives
他们愿意牺牲自己的生命
sacrifice their own lives
牺牲自己的生命
they are our comrades in arms.
他们是我们的战友。
Now we let our comrades in arms become enemies.
现在我们让战友变成了敌人。
How is this different from the others?
这与其他有什么不同？
Your thoughts are very scary.
你的想法非常可怕。
Do you want to be a traitor?
你想当叛徒吗？
Actually who is the traitor?
到底谁才是叛徒呢？
You make sure first.
你先确定一下。
That's the fifth bench?
这是第五个替补席吗？
We're pretending to talk here
我们在这里假装说话
wait for Chen Jia Ping and Jie's people to appear
等待陈家平和杰的人出现
immediately arrested
立即被捕
this time Chen Jia Ping definitely couldn't escape
这次陈家平肯定逃不掉了
look at her makeup
看看她的妆容
There he is?
他在那？
He sat in fifth place.
他坐在第五位。
He must have come to cooperate.
他一定是来合作的。
What should we do?
我们应该做什么？
The cooperating person has not yet appeared
合作者尚未出现
Chen Jia Ping seemed to be about to leave
陈家平似乎正要离开
not true
不对
just now
现在
his hand touched under the bench.
他的手摸到了长凳下面。
Maybe not to work together.
也许不会一起工作。
He must have exchanged information.
他肯定已经交换了信息。
Catch it immediately!
立即抓住它！
Catch him, caught red-handed.
抓住他，当场抓住。
Road!
路！
A little faster!
快一点！
Fast!
快速地！
Fast.
快速地。
Do not move.
不要动。
Raise your hand
举起你的手
chen Jia Ping
chen Jia Ping
Do you still want to avoid it this time?
这次你还想避免吗？
You...
你...
Ketua Zhao.
Ketua Zhao.
Why are you always everywhere?
为什么你总是无处不在？
What are you here for?
你为什么在这里？
Why am I here?
为什么我在这里？
I'm still asking why you came
我还在问你为什么来
why are you pointing a gun at me?
你为什么用枪指着我？
have you registered a permit to hold weapons in the French concession?
你有在法租界持有武器的许可证吗？
What are you holding under the bench
你在板凳底下拿着什么
seat?
座位？
There isn't anything.
什么都没有啊
Check the body.
检查身体。
Chief.
首席。
This is their territory
这是他们的领地
are you sure you want to do that?
您确定要这样做吗？
We have this ability,
我们有这个能力，
check the body.
检查身体。
Go away.
离开。
Search the bench.
搜索板凳。
There isn't any.
没有。
Youre here.
你在这里。
Police Clemish.
警察克莱米什。
You guys?
你们？
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Chief,
首席，
there was a misunderstanding between us.
我们之间存在误会。
Correct.
正确的。
That's right, right?
没错，对吧？
That's it.
就是这样。
Where is Captain Clemish?
克莱米什船长在哪里？
He will return to France for a while.
他将返回法国一段时间。
He asked me to look after his dog.
他让我照顾他的狗。
Sheriff Clemson walks the dog here every day.
克莱姆森警长每天都会在这里遛狗。
So, I'll just leave it at that.
所以，我就这样吧。
Why?
为什么？
Ketua Zhao
Ketua Zhao
do you mind?
你介意吗？
No opinion.
没有意见。
Do not mind.
别在意。
No comment. You pointed a gun at me earlier.
没有意见。你之前用枪指着我。
Why
为什么
want to shoot me?
想开枪打我吗？
Must be wrong
一定是错的
keep all the guns.
保留所有枪支。
If it's wrong
如果错了
do what must be done.
做必须做的事。
Sheriff Clemens.
克莱门斯警长。
Have a safe trip.
一路平安。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Until found.
直到被发现。
Chairman of the Fifth Transportation Station, Jin Ming
第五交通站站长金明
betrayed after being captured
被俘后被出卖
many comrades were betrayed by him
很多同志都被他出卖了
captured or sacrificed.
被俘或牺牲。
The loss is very painful.
失去是非常痛苦的。
Be sure to find the Jinming location
一定要找到金明位置
and report it immediately to the organization.
并立即向组织报告。
If there is an emergency,
如果有紧急情况，
call this number 65542.2.
请拨打此号码 65542.2。
Once the phone rings, hang up.
电话一响就挂断。
Call again
重拨
parrot
鹦鹉
based on Jin Ming level,
以金明等级为基础，
he can unlock the secret code of the link.
他可以解锁链接的密码。
But what he didn't know was,
但他不知道的是，
You contact the organization before being arrested
您在被捕前联系了该组织
before being arrested.
在被捕之前。
So the secret code for the parrot contacted me
于是鹦鹉的暗号联系了我
has been replaced with a second level secret code.
已被二级密码取代。
It cannot be solved by him.
这不是他能解决的。
However, maybe you can take advantage of this
然而，也许你可以利用这个
to lock Jinming.
to lock Jinming.
Actually in the hands of Luo Guanqun or Zhao An?
到底在罗冠群还是赵安手里？
First thing,
首先，
look for someone to make a new declaration.
寻找某人做出新的声明。
Place the contents of the paper in the notification section,
将论文内容放在通知部分，
however, it should be published tomorrow.
然而，它应该明天发布。
Second thing,
第二件事，
Why? Look at me.
为什么？看着我。
Should be.
应该。
Tomorrow at 2 pm
明天下午 2 点
you disguised yourself as me,
你把自己伪装成我，
go to Zhoushan Park.
去舟山公园。
What is it?
它是什么？
But if anyone notices
但如果有人注意到
that person is you,
那个人就是你
You have to think of a reason
你得想个理由
Tell them why you appeared here.
告诉他们你为什么出现在这里。
Waiter.
服务员。
Two!
二！
Where is guest room 612?
612号客房在哪里？
The master came out earlier.
大师先出来了。
Is this brat going to lie to us?
这小子是要骗我们吗？
What code?
什么代码？
Absolutely not true.
绝对不是真的。
He was not that brave.
他没那么勇敢。
There must be an error.
一定有错误。
After he comes home ask clearly,
回家后问清楚，
also quite brave
也相当勇敢
still dare to go out.
还是敢出去。
You're a new resident, right?
你是新居民，对吧？
Never seen it before.
以前从未见过。
New arrivals arrive on their first day of work.
新员工第一天上班。
You're the one who just arrived
你是刚来的那个
Please help, Brother.
请帮忙，兄弟。
What did you come to get?
你来是想得到什么？
Guest number 61 wants scented soap,
61号客人想要香皂，
it's there, right?
它就在那儿，对吧？
It's?
它是？
This soap seems moist.
这块肥皂看起来很湿润。
Brother, I've brought it.
兄弟，我已经带来了。
I know you can't smoke here.
我知道你不能在这里抽烟。
Don't talk carelessly outside.
不要在外面乱说话。
Chief.
首席。
Earlier someone came into room 612.
早些时候有人进入了612房间。
Who's that?
那是谁？
Waiter
服务员
waiter.
服务员。
No need to make a fuss anymore
无需再大惊小怪
Is there anyone?
有人吗?
Hello, sir.
你好先生。
Pujiang Hotel.
浦江宾馆。
House six one two.
六号一二号屋。
Hey!
嘿！
Sister.
姐姐。
I saw the Chief earlier
我之前就见过酋长
seems to be heading towards the grass.
似乎正在走向草地。
You pay attention.
你注意了。
Good.
好的。
Chief.
首席。
Do not move.
不要动。
Put the gun down.
把枪放下。
It's me
这就是我
why are you like this?
你为什么这样？
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
The food at this hotel is very bad.
这家酒店的食物非常糟糕。
I went out to eat some delicious food.
我出去吃一些美味的食物。
Aren't you afraid of your people looking for you?
你就不怕人家找你吗？
You don't even recognize me.
你甚至都不认识我了。
What am I afraid of?
我害怕什么？
We didn't arrest anyone today.
我们今天没有逮捕任何人。
Not caught.
没被抓住。
Impossible.
不可能的。
The code I translated was not wrong.
我翻译的代码没有错。
We'll talk inside.
我们会在里面说话。
Sister.
姐姐。
Didn't get caught, right?
没被抓到吧？
Thank you earlier.
早先谢谢你了。
Don't hesitate, don't hesitate.
别犹豫，别犹豫。
I have a pack of cigarettes
我有一包香烟
given by a friend
朋友给的
he said it was pretty good
他说这很好
but I don't smoke.
但我不抽烟。
How about giving it to you, Big Brother?
给你大哥怎么样？
I can't afford to buy
我买不起
I can't afford it.
我买不起。
That's right, right?
没错，对吧？
If not, just like this
如果没有，就这样
chief administrator
首席行政官
always walk around here.
总是在这里走来走去。
Brother, if you want to smoke, go outside
兄弟，你想抽烟就出去吧
for smokers.
对于吸烟者。
I'll help you watch it here.
我在这里帮你看一下。
Brother, come up.
兄弟，上来吧。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Otherwise our people
否则我们的人民
If I knew, I would cooperate with you.
如果我知道的话，我就会和你合作。
First, we issue a contact code.
首先，我们发布一个联系代码。
Then suddenly cancel the connection.
然后突然取消连接。
There's no point in saying all this.
说这些都没意义。
Brother Huang,
黄弟兄，
for your sake,
为你着想，
Village Chief Mu and I ran here and there.
我和穆村长跑来跑去。
The boss also agreed
老板也同意了
to send you
送你
to the new government construction department.
到新政府建设部门。
So, you...
那么你...
Still have some reservations,
还是有些保留的，
wasting our good intentions.
浪费了我们的好意。
Tonight I want to meet Village Chief Mu.
今晚我想见见穆村长。
Please tell me.
请告诉我。
You will definitely be given a big prize.
您一定会获得大奖。
Same with me.
和我一样。
I want to meet Kimura.
我想见见木村。
Good.
好的。
I will report to Village Chief Mu now.
我现在就向穆村长汇报。
Didn't have time to report to superiors
没有时间向上级汇报
must be killed immediately
必须立即杀死
brother
兄弟
The smoke...
烟...
Sister.
姐姐。
Just now the foreman came
刚才工头来了
the chief administrator said not to make a fuss
行政长官说不要大惊小怪
lower your voice.
降低你的声音。
Your scent is really nice.
你的气味真的很好闻。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Next time if there is a problem,
下次如果还有问题的话
Good.
好的。
Please look for me.
请找我。
Sister.
姐姐。
Then I'll deliver the goods.
那我就发货了。
Go, go.
走吧，走吧。
Delivering goods.
运送货物。
Good, go.
好，走吧。
Hello, sir.
你好先生。
Change bed linen.
更换床单。
I'm in the bathroom.
我在浴室里。
Come in.
进来。